Finding Aid to the Letters to Alfred Stieglitz, 1933-1944, undated MS.9
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
Letters to Alfred Stieglitz
1933-1944, undated
Georgia O'Keeffe Museum
O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986
Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001
Adams, Ansel, 1902-1984
MS.9
17
1.668 Linear Feet
The collection includes over letters primarily from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz dating from 1933 to 1944.
Related Materials
The bulk of the correspondence between O'Keeffe and Stieglitz is located in the Alfred Stieglitz / Georgia O'Keeffe Archive, Yale Collection of American Literature at the Beinecke Rare Book and Manuscript Library.
Selections from the O'Keeffe/Stieglitz correspondence has been published in the following:
Greenough, Sarah, ed. My Faraway One: Selected Letters of Georgia O'Keeffe and Alfred Stieglitz. Vol. 1 (1915-1933). New Haven: Yale University Press, 2011.
Arrangement of Collection
The collection is arranged chronologically. All enclosures are kept with associated letters, except in the case of photographic materials. Photographs have been separated out and follow the correspondence series.
Access Restrictions
The collection is open to the public for research purposes.
Scope and Contents
The collection includes 232 letters primarily from Georgia O'Keeffe (1887-1986)to her husband, Alfred Stieglitz (1864-1946), dating from 1933 to 1944. Between 1915 and 1946 O'Keeffe and Stieglitz exchanged over 5,000 letters; this is only a small sample of the rich correspondence between the two. The letters are personal in nature and discuss the lives and careers of O'Keeffe and Stieglitz. Some of the letters are "notes" left by O'Keeffe to be found by Stieglitz while she was in New Mexico. On these notes Stieglitz inscribes where and when he found them; for example, "Found in my slippers / Apr 28/43 / Georgia had left for New Mexico". A few of the letters include enclosures such as feathers, tissue paper, dried flowers, or pine needles. In a letter from 1944, O'Keeffe encloses two photographs of her Black Place paintings and one photograph of a pelvis bone painting.
Also included are three letters from Maria Chabot, one from "Ann", and one from Ansel Adams to Stieglitz.
Acquisition Information
The collection was an anonymous gift to the Georgia O'Keeffe Museum.
The collection is the physical property of the Georgia O'Keeffe Museum Research Center. The collection is subject to all copyright laws. The researcher assumes full responsibility for observing all copyright, property, and libel laws as they apply. Contact the Georgia O'Keeffe Museum Research Center Archivist for further copyright and publication information as it pertains to this collection.
Correspondence; Photographs; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946
- Correspondence, 1933-1944, undated; 1
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1933-10-6; MS-OKAS-0001; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
    Correspondence; Stieglitz, Alfred, 1864-1946
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1942-7-20; MS-OKAS-0002; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1942-10-8; MS-OKAS-0003; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-1-23; MS-OKAS-0004; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Note from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-4-28; MS-OKAS-0005; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Note which Georgia O'Keeffe left for Alfred Stieglitz in his slippers as she left for New Mexico. (Box 1)
  - Note from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-4-28; MS-OKAS-0006; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Note which Georgia O'Keeffe left for Alfred Stieglitz in his drawer as she left for New Mexico. (Box 1)
  - Note from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-4-28; MS-OKAS-0007; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Note to Alfred Stieglitz from Georgia O'Keeffe - she left on the table for him as she left for New Mexico. (Box 1)
  - Note from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-4-28; MS-OKAS-0008; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Note to Alfred Stieglitz from Georgia O'Keeffe - she left note in wrapper for him as she left for New Mexico. (Box 1)
  - Note from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-4-28; MS-OKAS-0009; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Note to Alfred Stieglitz from Georgia O'Keeffe - she left in his bed as she left for New Mexico. (Box 1)
  - Note from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-4-28; MS-OKAS-0010; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Note to Alfred Stieglitz from Georgia O'Keeffe - she left in his coat as she left for New Mexico. (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-4-28; MS-OKAS-0011; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-4-29; MS-OKAS-0012; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-4-30; MS-OKAS-0013; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-4-30; MS-OKAS-0014; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Telegram from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-4-30; MS-OKAS-0015; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-1; MS-OKAS-0016; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-2; MS-OKAS-0017; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-4; MS-OKAS-0018; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-4; MS-OKAS-0019; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-5; MS-OKAS-0020; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-6; MS-OKAS-0021; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-7; MS-OKAS-0022; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-10; MS-OKAS-0023; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-10; MS-OKAS-0024; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz, undated; MS-OKAS-0025; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-12; MS-OKAS-0026; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-13; MS-OKAS-0027; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-15; MS-OKAS-0028; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Maria Chabot to Alfred Stieglitz, undated; MS-OKAS-0029; Chabot, Maria, 1913-2001 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-17; MS-OKAS-0030; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-13; MS-OKAS-0031; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-19; MS-OKAS-0032; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-18; MS-OKAS-0033; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-22; MS-OKAS-0034; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-24; MS-OKAS-0035; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 1)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-25; MS-OKAS-0036; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-26; MS-OKAS-0037; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-27; MS-OKAS-0038; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-28; MS-OKAS-0039; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-29; MS-OKAS-0040; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5-31; MS-OKAS-0041; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Envelope from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-5; MS-OKAS-0230; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-1; MS-OKAS-0042; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-2; MS-OKAS-0043; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-15; MS-OKAS-0044; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-7; MS-OKAS-0045; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-8; MS-OKAS-0046; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-12; MS-OKAS-0047; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-13; MS-OKAS-0048; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-14; MS-OKAS-0049; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-14; MS-OKAS-0050; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-16; MS-OKAS-0051; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-17; MS-OKAS-0052; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-18; MS-OKAS-0053; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-19; MS-OKAS-0054; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-22; MS-OKAS-0055; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-23; MS-OKAS-0056; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-24; MS-OKAS-0057; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-25; MS-OKAS-0058; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-26; MS-OKAS-0059; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-28; MS-OKAS-0060; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-6-29; MS-OKAS-0061; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 2)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-1; MS-OKAS-0062; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-2; MS-OKAS-0063; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-3; MS-OKAS-0064; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-5; MS-OKAS-0065; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-7; MS-OKAS-0066; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-8; MS-OKAS-0067; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-10; MS-OKAS-0068; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-10; MS-OKAS-0069; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-11; MS-OKAS-0070; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-12; MS-OKAS-0071; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-14; MS-OKAS-0072; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-15; MS-OKAS-0073; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7; MS-OKAS-0074; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-19; MS-OKAS-0075; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-18; MS-OKAS-0076; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-12; MS-OKAS-0077; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-20; MS-OKAS-0078; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-20; MS-OKAS-0079; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-21; MS-OKAS-0080; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-22; MS-OKAS-0081; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-23; MS-OKAS-0082; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-24; MS-OKAS-0083; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-26; MS-OKAS-0084; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-27; MS-OKAS-0085; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Ann to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-28; MS-OKAS-0086 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-30; MS-OKAS-0087; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943-7-31; MS-OKAS-0088; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Envelope from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1943; MS-OKAS-0231; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 3)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-17; MS-OKAS-0089; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz left in Stieglitz's bed. (Box 4)
  - Note from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-17; MS-OKAS-0090; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Note from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz left in Stieglitz's bed. (Box 4)
  - Note from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-17; MS-OKAS-0091; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Note from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz left in Stieglitz's "wrapper". (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-18; MS-OKAS-0092; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-19; MS-OKAS-0093; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-19; MS-OKAS-0094; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-19; MS-OKAS-0095; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-19; MS-OKAS-0096; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, undated; MS-OKAS-0097; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-20; MS-OKAS-0098; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-21; MS-OKAS-0099; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-22; MS-OKAS-0100; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-24; MS-OKAS-0101; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-25; MS-OKAS-0102; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-26; MS-OKAS-0103; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-27; MS-OKAS-0104; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-28; MS-OKAS-0105; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-4-29; MS-OKAS-0106; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-1; MS-OKAS-0107; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-2; MS-OKAS-0108; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-3; MS-OKAS-0109; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-4; MS-OKAS-0110; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-5; MS-OKAS-0111; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Envelope from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-6; MS-OKAS-0112; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; No items enclosed. (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-6; MS-OKAS-0113; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-8; MS-OKAS-0114; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-9; MS-OKAS-0115; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Tissue and flower enclosed. (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-10; MS-OKAS-0116; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 4)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-12; MS-OKAS-0117; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-13; MS-OKAS-0118; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-15; MS-OKAS-0119; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-16; MS-OKAS-0120; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-17; MS-OKAS-0121; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-18; MS-OKAS-0122; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-24; MS-OKAS-0123; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-25; MS-OKAS-0124; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-26; MS-OKAS-0125; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-27; MS-OKAS-0126; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-5-29; MS-OKAS-0127; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-10; MS-OKAS-0128; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-10; MS-OKAS-0129; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-10; MS-OKAS-0130; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-10; MS-OKAS-0131; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-10; MS-OKAS-0132; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-10; MS-OKAS-0133; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-10; MS-OKAS-0134; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-10; MS-OKAS-0135; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-10; MS-OKAS-0136; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-12; MS-OKAS-0137; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-14; MS-OKAS-0138; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-15; MS-OKAS-0139; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-16; MS-OKAS-0140; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-17; MS-OKAS-0141; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 5)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-17; MS-OKAS-0142; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-19; MS-OKAS-0143; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-21; MS-OKAS-0144; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-22; MS-OKAS-0145; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-23; MS-OKAS-0146; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-6-24; MS-OKAS-0147; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-3; MS-OKAS-0148; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-5; MS-OKAS-0149; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz with enclosed photographs, 1944-7-6; MS-OKAS-0150; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz sent from New Mexico. Enclosed are photographs of Georgia O'Keeffe's paintings of Black Place I (CR1080), Black Place III (CR1082) and Pelvis I (CR1075). (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-8; MS-OKAS-0151; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, undated; MS-OKAS-0152; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-10; MS-OKAS-0153; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-12; MS-OKAS-0154; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-12; MS-OKAS-0155; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-14; MS-OKAS-0156; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-17; MS-OKAS-0157; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-17; MS-OKAS-0158; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-17; MS-OKAS-0159; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-18; MS-OKAS-0160; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-18; MS-OKAS-0161; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-19; MS-OKAS-0162; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-20; MS-OKAS-0163; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986; Enclosed letter to Hudson Walker. (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-21; MS-OKAS-0164; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, undated; MS-OKAS-0165; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-24; MS-OKAS-0166; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-25; MS-OKAS-0167; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-26; MS-OKAS-0168; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-27; MS-OKAS-0169; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-29; MS-OKAS-0170; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 6)
  - Letter from Georgia O'Keeffe to Alfred Stieglitz, 1944-7-31; MS-OKAS-0171; O'Keeffe, Georgia, 1887-1986 (Box 7)